Unfortunately, they're both on our side.
Best Defense is a comedy, war film directed by Willard Huyck.
An engineer fails to get the bugs out of a tank before
an Army officer has to use it in Kuwait.
Wylie, played by Dudley Moore.
Landry, played by Eddie Murphy.
Laura, played by Kate Capshaw.
Loparino, played by George Dzundza.
Claire, played by Helen Shaver.
Brank, played by Mark Arnott.
Best Defense is a 1984 American action comedy film,
starring Dudley Moore and Eddie Murphy.
The original music score was composed by Patrick Williams.
It was released by Paramount Pictures.
The film follows the lives of Wylie Cooper and T.M.
Landry, two different characters who never interact.
One of the two sub-plots involves Cooper, an engineer who tries to develop a new gyroscope
for tanks, and eventually uses the design plans of a murdered competitor.
The other subplot involves Landry, a tank commander who accidentally wanders
into a war zone while trying to navigate a poorly designed tank.
The film was released on July 20, 1984, grossing a total of $19 million at
the box office, and received negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of army, middle east, armor, kgb, engineer.
The tone is lighthearted.